Daphner Aulibrice

Software Engineer

Email: aulibriced@gmail.com Portfolio: adaphner.github.io

Experienced software engineer. Decorated and highly energetic leader with 11+ years of work experience and proven knowledge of software application development. Strong skills in project planning, problem-solving, and detailed analysis related to system design and process improvement.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FiconXD.com

West Palm Beach, FL

Jan 2020 - Current

Software Engineer

- Developed robust, reusable, and reliable components to enhance the company platforms, frameworks, and services.
- Performed cross-browser testing and remediation for 100 percent of front-end web applications to ensure performance and superior visual quality.
- Analyzed user needs and software requirements to determine the feasibility of design within the allocated time and cost constraints.

Florida International University

Miami, FL

Programming Learning Assistant

Aug 2018 - Dec 2020

- Improved students' average test scores by 15 percent within the first few weeks of small group tutoring sessions to reinforce key programming concepts.
- Increased the retention rate of key programming concepts by 20 percent by leading small class presentations using lectures and class discussions.
- Provided valuable feedback and graded 60 to 70 exams each week with 100 percent accuracy.

Department of State

Quantico, VA

Marine Safety Officer

Mar 2015 - Aug 2018

- Managed and operated internal security systems to designated U.S. diplomatic and consular facilities to prevent the compromise of classified information and equipment vital to the national security of the United States.
- Provided protection for U.S. citizens and U.S. government property located within designated U.S. diplomatic and consular premises during exigent circumstances.
- Directly managed security infrastructure and daily operations of security systems.

U.S. Marine Corps

Washington, DC

Flight Equipment Technician | Collateral Duty Inspector

Jul 2011 - Mar 2015

- Maintained 100 percent mission readiness by testing, calibrating, and performing weekly operational checks on all mission-critical aircraft systems and computer systems.
- Increased all benchmark and performance parameters by 30 percent on all mission-critical components.
- Awarded the Navy and Marine Corps Achievement Medal for exceptional and superior professional performance and achievements.

EDUCATION

FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Miami, FL

B.S. Information Technology Graduated Magna Cum Laude

Aug 2018 - Dec 2020

SKILLS

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | React | Node | Express | Java | Python | Flask | MySQL | MongoDB